Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Spring Fever= =Episode 21=
=حمى الربيع= =الحلقة 21=
A'man.
أمان.
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
A'man,
أمان،
wh-what's wrong?
ماذا هناك؟
What did you do to me?
ماذا فعلت بي؟
What?
ماذا؟
I didn't do anything.
لم أفعل شيئا.
A'man.
أمان.
A'man, wait for me.
آمين، انتظرني.
My lord, it's the blue whistle.
سيدي، إنها الصافرة الزرقاء.
It seems they found the groom of Duting Station.
يبدو أنهم وجدوا عريس محطة دوتينغ.
I'll take men there now.
سوف آخذ الرجال إلى هناك الآن.
When you arrive, evacuate him quickly.
عندما تصل، قم بإخلائه بسرعة.
Understood.
مفهومة.
A'man.
أمان.
Don't touch me!
لا تلمسني!
Did I hurt you?
هل أذيتك؟
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
أنا آسف. أنا آسف.
But
لكن
you're my concubine.
أنت محظيتي.
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
You're my woman.
أنت امرأتي.
- You won't let me touch you. - Don't come closer.
- لن تسمح لي بلمسك. - لا تقترب.
Who do you want touching you?
من تريد أن يلمسك؟
Lu Shi'an, let me go!
لو شيآن، دعني أذهب!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Why can't I touch you?
لماذا لا أستطيع لمسك؟
No!
لا!
For Jin's sake,
من أجل جين،
I'm begging you.
انا أتوسل إليك.
I beg you, please.
أتوسل إليك من فضلك.
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
A'man.
أمان.
I'm begging you.
انا أتوسل إليك.
Forgive me.
سامحني.
I beg you.
أرجوك.
I truly can't control myself.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع السيطرة على نفسي.
My lord,
سيدي،
I never thought they'd fight
لم أكن أعتقد أنهم سيقاتلون
so desperately. I underestimated them.
لقد قللت من شأنهم.
It's not your fault.
إنه ليس خطؤك.
The groom wasn't taken far.
لم يتم أخذ العريس بعيدًا.
After them!
بعدهم!
- Understood!
- مفهوم!
They should catch up.
ينبغي عليهم اللحاق بالركب.
Your hand...
يدك...
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
Handle the cleanup. I'll return first.
سأتولى أمر التنظيف. سأعود أولاً.
Okay.
تمام.
(It's unbearable. The drug's too strong.)
(إنه أمر لا يطاق. الدواء قوي جدًا.)
(My whole body's burning up.)
(جسدي كله يحترق.)
A'man?
امان؟
A'man!
أمان!
A'man.
أمان.
(Shen Que.)
(شين كيو)
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I...
أنا...
I can't. Stay back!
لا أستطيع. ابقى في الخلف!
A'man. A'man!
أمان. أمان!
Stay back.
ابقى في الخلف.
I just want to help you.
أريد فقط أن أساعدك.
You've taken Heye Powder?
هل أخذت Heye Powder؟
Was it Lu Shi'an?
هل كان لو شيآن؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Was it Lu Shi'an? I'll kill him!
هل كان لو شيآن؟ سأقتله!
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Don't go kill him.
لا تذهب لتقتله.
Why?
لماذا؟
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
I can't let anyone know I'm here.
لا أستطيع أن أخبر أحداً أنني هنا.
A'man,
أمان،
let's find a physician,
دعونا نجد طبيبا
okay?
تمام؟
A'man, I'll find a physician.
يا رجل سأبحث عن طبيب.
Wait here. You'll be fine.
انتظر هنا، ستكون بخير.
Don't leave.
لا تغادر.
This can't get out.
هذا لا يمكن أن يخرج.
A'man! A'man!
أمان! أمان!
Are you insane?
هل انت مجنون؟
Soak in cold water for an hour.
نقعها في الماء البارد لمدة ساعة.
It'll neutralize the drug.
سوف يحيد الدواء.
♪Grind flesh between grit and stone♪
♪طحن اللحم بين الحصى والحجر♪
♪Sink into pain, only then are pearls born♪
♪الغرق في الألم، حينها فقط تولد اللآلئ♪
♪Wait until abyssal darkness stains every inch of skin♪
♪انتظر حتى يلطخ الظلام السحيق كل شبر من الجلد♪
Don't be afraid. I won't let anything happen to you.
لا تخف، لن أسمح بحدوث أي شيء لك.
It hurts.
إنه يؤلمني.
♪I'll sweep through dusty sands♪
♪سأمسح الرمال المتربة♪
♪Passing wind♪
♪ريح عابرة♪
Stay still. Endure it.
ابقى ساكنًا. تحمل ذلك.
I'm freezing.
أنا متجمد.
Just bear it a little longer.
فقط تحمل الأمر لفترة أطول قليلاً.
♪Bathing in affection♪
♪الاستحمام في المودة♪
♪Condensing into rain♪
♪تكثف إلى مطر♪
Don't worry. I'm here.
لا تقلق، أنا هنا.
Shen Que, I fell terrible.
شين كيو، لقد سقطت بشكل رهيب.
Shen Que.
شين كيو.
♪Henceforth we walk the mortal realm♪
♪من الآن فصاعدا نسير في عالم البشر♪
♪Across vast mountains and rivers♪
♪عبر الجبال والأنهار الشاسعة♪
Lu Shi'an. Lu Shi'an!
لو شيان. لو شيان!
My lord,
سيدي،
does the Inner Bureau also meddle in my bed affairs with a concubine?
هل يتدخل المكتب الداخلي أيضًا في شؤون سريرتي مع محظية؟
You drugged and violated her. I can charge you for this.
لقد خدّرتها واعتديت عليها. يمكنني أن أتهمك بذلك.
I didn't drug her! Someone tampered with it!
لم أُخدّرها! أحدهم تلاعب بها!
You can investigate freely.
يمكنك التحقيق بحرية.
But when the time comes, let everyone hear
ولكن عندما يحين الوقت، فليسمع الجميع
whether I'm truly guilty,
هل أنا مذنب حقا،
or Ye Qinglan and you are illicitly involved.
أو Ye Qinglan وأنت متورط بشكل غير مشروع.
What?
ماذا؟
Why don't you explain?
لماذا لا تشرح؟
Getting nervous?
هل تشعر بالتوتر؟
Let me make this clear.
دعني أوضح هذا.
I spare your life
انا انقذ حياتك
because you're Jin's father,
لأنك والد جين،
and you once took in Ye Qinglan.
وقد أخذت مرة واحدة في Ye Qinglan.
For that kindness,
من أجل هذا اللطف،
I'm grateful.
أنا ممتن.
But if you dare harm her again in any way,
ولكن إذا تجرأت على إيذائها مرة أخرى بأي شكل من الأشكال،
I won't hesitate to wipe out the Lu family.
لن أتردد في القضاء على عائلة لو.
Understood?
مفهوم؟
Did I hurt you?
هل أذيتك؟
I'm sorry. I came late.
انا آسف لقد جئت متأخرا.
It was not your fault.
لم يكن خطؤك.
I never expected Lu Shi'an to drug me either.
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن يقوم لو شيآن بإعطائي المخدر أيضًا.
Your hand is injured.
يدك مجروحة.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Just an accident last night.
مجرد حادث الليلة الماضية.
H-Have I caused any trouble?
ح-هل سببت أي مشكلة؟
A'man,
أمان،
come back to me,
عُد إلي،
okay?
تمام؟
I don't want it to happen again.
لا أريد أن يحدث هذا مرة أخرى.
I'm just a criminal slave,
أنا مجرد عبد مجرم
and a woman who
وامرأة
bore another man's child.
أنجبت طفلاً لرجل آخر.
You're different.
أنت مختلف.
You are an official.
أنت مسؤول.
A noble person
شخص نبيل
with power and status,
مع القوة والمكانة،
yet to be married.
لم تتزوج بعد.
I don't want you to waste
لا أريدك أن تضيع
all your time
كل وقتك
and energy on me.
والطاقة عليّ.
I can take care of myself.
أنا أستطيع أن أعتني بنفسي.
A'man, we're close to the truth.
يا رجل، نحن قريبون من الحقيقة.
We're investigating those who worked in Duting Station.
نحن نحقق مع الأشخاص الذين عملوا في محطة دوتينغ.
Once we find the culprit,
بمجرد العثور على الجاني،
we can clear your family's name.
يمكننا تبرئة اسم عائلتك.
I thank you on behalf of my father and brother.
أشكركم نيابة عن والدي وأخي.
Since when do we need to say thanks?
منذ متى أصبحنا بحاجة إلى أن نقول شكرا؟
You're being too distant with me.
أنت بعيدة جدًا عني.
Well...
حسنًا...
Guess who knocked out Lu Shi'an last night?
تخمين من الذي ضرب لو شيآن الليلة الماضية؟
Knocked out?
هل تم إقصاؤك؟
So
لذا
you didn't...
لم تفعل...
Didn't what?
لم ماذا؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Help!
يساعد!
Let go!
اتركه!
I refuse.
انا ارفض.
Get out!
اخرج!
♪Autumn wind stirs ripples of change♪
♪رياح الخريف تثير تموجات التغيير♪
♪Never saw flowers bloom with fragrant abundance♪
♪لم أرى الزهور تتفتح بوفرة عطرة♪
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I am helping myself too.
أنا أساعد نفسي أيضاً.
♪Sighing that all lives are tied to fate♪
♪تنهد بأن كل الأرواح مرتبطة بالقدر♪
♪Yet in this life our destined bond is but a fleeting illusion♪
♪ومع ذلك، في هذه الحياة، فإن رباطنا المقدر ليس سوى وهم عابر♪
♪Though drowned in love's embrace♪
♪على الرغم من الغرق في أحضان الحب♪
♪Scars now mark my weary face♪
♪الندوب الآن تترك علامات على وجهي المتعب♪
♪Love and hate through fleeting years, memories fade with falling tears♪
♪الحب والكراهية عبر السنين العابرة، والذكريات تتلاشى مع الدموع المتساقطة♪
♪Flickering candlelight disturbs♪
♪ضوء الشموع المتذبذب يزعج♪
(Lu Shi'an, I know you don't love me.)
(لو شيآن، أعلم أنك لا تحبني.)
(Not even like me.)
(لا يشبهني حتى.)
♪Beckons me to chase the sun♪
♪يدعوني لمطاردة الشمس♪
(But... but I don't care.)
(ولكن... ولكنني لا أهتم.)
(Because no one in this world loves me anymore.)
(لأن لا أحد في هذا العالم يحبني بعد الآن.)
♪Though drowned in love's embrace♪
♪على الرغم من الغرق في أحضان الحب♪
♪Scars now mark my weary face♪
♪الندوب الآن تترك علامات على وجهي المتعب♪
♪Love and hate through fleeting years, memories fade with falling tears♪
♪الحب والكراهية عبر السنين العابرة، والذكريات تتلاشى مع الدموع المتساقطة♪
♪Flickering candlelight disturbs♪
♪ضوء الشموع المتذبذب يزعج♪
A'man.
أمان.
♪A fleeting dream so sweetly spun♪
♪ حلم عابر تم نسجه بشكل جميل ♪
(It's fine. I just)
(لا بأس. أنا فقط)
(want another child of ours.)
(نريد طفلًا آخر لنا.)
(That way, someone will love me.)
(بهذه الطريقة سوف يحبني شخص ما.)
(Maybe then, between you and me,)
(ربما حينها بيني وبينك)
(old grudges would melt away.)
(ستذوب الضغائن القديمة).
I never expected it to be her.
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن تكون هي.
You wouldn't understand women's matters.
لن تفهم أمور المرأة.
I truly don't understand.
أنا حقا لا أفهم.
But as long as she doesn't harm you, I won't interfere.
ولكن طالما أنها لا تؤذيك، فلن أتدخل.
Could you find me some clean clothes?
هل يمكنك أن تجد لي بعض الملابس النظيفة؟
Why?
لماذا؟
To go back.
للعودة.
Ye Qinglan, you're truly obstinate.
يي تشينغلان، أنت عنيد حقًا.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
But not now.
ولكن ليس الآن.
♪Grind flesh between grit and stone♪
♪طحن اللحم بين الحصى والحجر♪
♪Sink into pain, only then are pearls born♪
♪الغرق في الألم، حينها فقط تولد اللآلئ♪
♪Wait until abyssal darkness stains every inch of skin♪
♪انتظر حتى يلطخ الظلام السحيق كل شبر من الجلد♪
♪Then comes the time to chase the dawn♪
♪ثم يأتي الوقت لمطاردة الفجر♪
♪I'll sweep through dusty sands♪
♪سأمسح الرمال المتربة♪
♪Passing wind♪
♪ريح عابرة♪
♪Entwine my hair in dance♪
♪تشابك شعري في الرقص♪
♪I'll lean into his embrace♪
♪سأستند إلى حضنه♪
♪Wade through deep seas♪
♪خوض البحار العميقة♪
♪Bathing in affection♪
♪الاستحمام في المودة♪
♪Condensing into rain♪
♪تكثف إلى مطر♪
♪Who cast a frantic, lingering glance♪
♪الذي ألقى نظرة محمومة ومتباطئة♪
♪Carrying endless tenderness♪
♪تحمل حنانًا لا نهاية له♪
♪Gazing through eons of moonlit winds♪
♪التحديق عبر عصور من الرياح المضاءة بالقمر♪
♪Turn tears to pearls and cradle them within♪
♪حوّل الدموع إلى لآلئ واحتضنها في داخلك♪
♪Henceforth we walk the mortal realm♪
♪من الآن فصاعدا نسير في عالم البشر♪
♪Across vast mountains and rivers♪
♪عبر الجبال والأنهار الشاسعة♪
♪I'll sweep through dusty sands♪
♪سأمسح الرمال المتربة♪
♪Passing wind♪
♪ريح عابرة♪
♪Entwine my hair in dance♪
♪تشابك شعري في الرقص♪
♪I'll lean into his embrace♪
♪سأستند إلى حضنه♪
♪Wade through deep seas♪
♪خوض البحار العميقة♪
♪Bathing in affection♪
♪الاستحمام في المودة♪
♪Condensing into rain♪
♪تكثف إلى مطر♪